<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ZooTopia Directory</string>
    <string name="action_information">Information</string>
    <string name="action_uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="phone">TEL:888–888–8888</string>
    <string name="zoo_name">ZooTopia</string>
    <string name="alert_name">!! WARNING !!</string>
    <string name="alert_message"> This animal is very scary.
        Are you sure you would like to proceed?.</string>

    <string-array name="animal_names_full">
        <item>Gorilla</item>
        <item>Lion</item>
        <item>Penguin</item>
        <item>Red Panda</item>
        <item>Zebra</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="animal_descriptions_full">
        <item name="gorilla_description">
            These ground-dwelling herbivorous apes are the largest living primates, and they are the next closest living relatives to humans after the chimpanzees and bonobos.
            Like all the great apes, the arms of the gorilla are longer than its legs.
            Though they can stand upright, they usually use their arms as legs, a characteristic known as knuckle walking.
            Gorillas are usually surprisingly shy, though they may show aggression by beating their chests and charging if their social group is threatened.
        </item>
        <item name="lion_description">
          A king of the animal kingdom, a lion is a muscular, deep-chested cat with a short head and a prominent mane.
        Being the biggest of the cat species, lions are excellent combat animals despite their wildness.
        </item>
        <item name="penguin_description">
            An aquatic, flightless bird, only found in arctic regions.
            Often seen in massive flocks, penguins are fierce when cornered, and can quickly overrun any hunter incompetent enough to get close to them.
        </item>
        <item name="redpanda_description">
            The red panda is a small mammal, slightly larger than a domestic cat, with a bear-like body and thick russet fur.
            The belly and limbs are black, and there are white markings on the side of the head and above its small eyes.
            Red pandas are very skillful and acrobatic animals that predominantly stay in trees.
            It is a solitary animal, mainly active from dusk to dawn, though they can be quite affectionate if properly tamed.
        </item>
        <item name="zebra_description">
            A member of the horse family native to arid and desert areas.
            Whilst it doesn\t share the same bodysize as a horse, due to years of evolution it\s one of the fastest hooved animals.
         </item>
    </string-array>


</resources>